justthejob.co.za 2013-04-30

# privacy policy

At **justthejob.co.za** , we take your privacy seriously! Please read this **Statement of Privacy** to be more aware about our policy on collecting, using and disclosing personal information. This website is not intended under the age of 16.

_Scope of Coverage_

This **Statement of Privacy** covers how **justthejob.co.** za treats personal information collected and received, including information relating to the past use of our products and services. "Personal Information" refers to information that personally identifies you by your name, email address or telephone number and other information that is not otherwise available publicly. This **Statement of** **Privacy** applies only to the practices of **justthejob.co.za** and the people we employ or manage. Other websites or services linked to/from this website will have their own statments of privacy which can be viewed by clicking on their respective privacy links.

_Collection of your Personal Information_

**justthejob.co.za** collects personal information, such as your name, email address or telephone number, work experience and other such data associated with a resume for job applications. When you register with **justthejob.co.za** and sign in to our services, you are no longer unknown to us.

**justthejob.co.za**  keeps track of your transactions with us and some of our affiliated business partners including information about your use of the services we offer. 

**justthejob.co.za** also keeps track of the pages our users visit within **justthejob.co.za** , for business and security purposes. We may use this data to deliver customised content and advertising to users whose behaviour indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

**justthejob.co.za** uses the collected information for the following general purposes: customising the advertisement and content you see, fulfilling your requests for services, improving our services, contacting you, conducting research and providing relevant reports for our internal and external clients.

**justthejob.co.za** may also collect certain information about your computer hardware and software. This information includes your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. We use this information for operating our services, maintaining the quality of the service, security, management and providing reports for relevant business purposes.

**justthe job.co.za** uses Just the Job to provide registration and sign-in services. If you create a MyJusttheJob account, you are simultaneously registering with **justthejob.co.za** and opening a MyJusttheJob account. All the registration information you provide is stored by us in your MyJusttheJob profile. For more information about a MyJusttheJob account, please visit [www.justthejob.co.za](http://www.justthejob.co.za/)

Please keep in mind that when you apply for vacancies advertised on **justthejob.co.za** , your resume data in MyJusttheJob account and any other information you disclosed during your job application will be made available to the companies you are applying to. We encourage you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to browse that are linked from **justthejob.co.za** so that you can understand how those webistes collect, use and share your information. We are not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on such websites outside the **justthejob.co.za** domain name.

_Use of your Personal Information_

**justthejob.co.za** does not sell, rent or share your personal information with other people or non-affiliated third parties excpet to provide you with the services you have requested. When you give us permission, or under these circumstances:

  * When you apply to jobs through our services, your resume data in MyJusttheJob account and any other information you disclosed during your job applications, will be made available to the companies you are applying to.
  * We encourage you to evaluate interview requests carefully and only confirm those you want to attend. Employers have the right to access any record of no-show or late cancellations to confirmed interview appointments.
  * Besides that, you may also opt for making your resume searchable by companies who use the **justthejob.co.za** "Searchable Resume Database" to recruit. The companies may retain a copy of your resume in their own files or databases. Though we endeavour to ensure that the companies comply with the relevant privacy laws, **justthejob.co.za** is not responsible for the retention, use or privacy of resumes by them or by any third party that could be related to or associatedwith these companies. You may opt for "Hide My Resume Search" to retain the full privacy of your resume and personal data.
  * **justthejob.co.za** works with business partners to provide some services. We provide the information only to trusted business partners who work with us or on our behalf under confidentiality agreements. Our business partners may use your information to help us communicate with you, about offers from them or **justthejob.co.za**. However, our business partners do not have any independent right to share this information;
  * **justthejob.co.za** observes the process of law and will establish or exercise our legal rights or defend ourselves in any legal claims;
  * **justthejob.co.za** believes in sharing the information in order to investigate, prevent or act on illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violation of **justthejob.co.za** Terms of Use, or as otherwise required by law;
  * Personal information collected on this site may be stored and processed in any country in which **justthejob.co.za** or it's business partners, any subsidiaries or agents who maintain facilities, and by using this site, you consent to any such transfer of information outside our country.

_Control of your Personal Information_

**justthejob.co.za** offers you various choices for the use and sharing of your personal information, as well as subscription to various marketing preferences and services. You may go to theMyJusttheJob account page to edit your personal information and preferences at any time. You may choose not to receive any marketing material from **justthejob.co.za** or from any of our affiliated partners. You may aslo subscribe to additional services from this account.

In addition, you may visit **justthejob.co.za** to view, edit or delete your personal information or discontinue your subscription to marketing preferences or services from **justthejob.co.za** database.

In both cases, described above, you will be asked to make your requests while logged into a MyJusttheJob account, so that **justthejob.co.za** can associate your preferences with a particular service. This security safeguard prevents someone else from making choices about the usage and control of your personal information. If you do not have a MyJusttheJob account, you can create one by 

You may also stop the delivery of future promotional emails from **justthejob.co.za** by following the specific instructions in the emails you receive or in the MyJusttheJob account page. The instruction explains how to stop receiving such mails.

However, there are some **justthejob.co.za** services which are sent out periodically by email to inform you of technical service issues, product surveys, new feature announcements and news about our services. You will be unable to unsubscribe from these emails as they are considered an integral part of the service you have chosen.

In the event **justthejob.co.za** goes through a business transition as a merger, acquisition by another company or sale of all or a portion of it's assets, your personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred.  You will be notified by email of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information and can choose to delete all your personal information.

_Security of your Personal Information_

**justthejob.co.za** is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorised access, use or disclosure. For example, your information is stored on computer systems that are located in controlled facilities. When **justthejob.co.za** transmits highly confidential information (such as a credit card number) over the Internet, we protect it through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.

_Email to Friend_

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about a job or our site, **justthejob.co.za** will ask you for your friend's name and email address. A one-time email inviting your friend will be send automatically. **justthejob.co.za** stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral programme.

_Resume References_

If you choose to add references to your resume, **justthejob.co.za** will ask for their names, telephone numbers, email addresses and position titles. This information will be enclosed as part of your job application and employers may contact them to get references for your applications.

_**justthejob.co.za** Newsletters_

When you subscribe to a **justthejob.co.za** Newsletter, we shall request your email address, in order to send you the newsletter(s) you have requested. You may subscribe and unsubscribe to the newsletters by following the prominent instructions mentioned in each of the newsletters.

_Service Providers_

**justthejob.co.za** may use third parties to provide 1) payment gateway services for optional services 2) a profiling/assessment service and 3) web analytics on our website. When you sign up for such services or by using our website, they may collect some information (e.g. credit card numbers, name) as necessary for the third party to provide that service.

These third parties are prohibited from using your personally indentifiable information for any other purpose.

_Testimonials/Success Stories_

**justthejob.co.za** will ask your permission to post your testimonial or success story. If you agree to post your story on this site, you should be aware that any personally indetifiable information you submit can be read, collected or used by other users of this site and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. **justthejob.co.za** will not be responsible for the personally indentifiable information you may choose to submit in these testimonials/success stories. 

_Changes to this Statement_

**justthejob.co.za** will occasionally update this **Statement of Privacy** to reflect company and user feedback. When we post changes to this statement, you will see the word "Updated" next to the **Privacy Statement** link on the front page of **justthejob.co.za.**  If there are material changes to this Statement or in the manner, **justthejob.co.za** will use your personal information, we shall psot a prominent notice on the website 30 calendar days prior to implementing the change.

**justthejob.co.za** encourages you to review this Statement periodically to be informed of how we are protecting your personal information.

_Contact Information_

justthejob.co.za welcomes your comments regarding the Statement of Privacy. If you believe we have not adhered to this statement, please contact us via the following:

Email:                                    info@justthejob.co.za

Postal Address:                      PO Box 1360, Jukskei Park, 2153

Physical Address:                  66A Stiglingh Road, Rivonia

Telephone Number:                011 807 2233

Fax Number:                           011 803 8920

_This Privacy Statement is effective from ....._

_This document was updated on ....._
